# Kier T Vasquez

.NET Developer



- 🔀 kiervasquez98@gmail.com 📞 09218131939

  - P E Sabellano St. Genes Compound, Quiot
    - 🛗 01/01/1998 🏲 Filipino 💄 Male

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/kiervasquez/

#### **Skills**

Programming (C#, HTML/CSS, .NET Development, Javascript, React, Vue), Databases (MySQL, Microsoft SQL Server, PostgreSQL),

Code Repository (BitBucket, Github, Team Foundation Server)

#### **Awards**

# **Accenture's Program the future**

#### 2017

• made it to the final 15 out of 100+ teams nationwide.

# STEaM Cup: Hack IT Challenge

#### 2019

- Manage a team of students on the Hackit challenge where they pitch contestants from different school to create an application.
- Won 1st Place

#### **Certificates**

- Philippine National I.T. Standards (PhilNITS) Foundation Inc., Cebu City, Philippines — Fundamental Information Technology Engineer
- Proxor, Cebu City, Philippines Proxor 3

#### **Education**

## Bachelor's Degree,

Cebu Institute of Technology - University 2014 – 2018 | Cebu City, Philippines

#### **Profile**

As a software developer with 5 years of experience. I have worked in various projects with different specs as a full stack developer and being flexible at most programming languages which also gave me strong communication and collaboration skills. My commitment to learning and staying up-to-date with the latest technologies enables me to deliver successful projects that exceed client expectations.

#### **Professional Experience**

#### Full Stack Developer, Fullscale Inc.

01/2021 - Present | CEBU CITY (CAPITAL), Philippines

- Tested programs and databases to identify issues and make necessary modifications
- Design, develop and implemented software application for website based on analyzed requirements and understanding of industry technical standards
- Revised, modularized and updated old code bases to modern development standard and improving functionality
- Work with teams and collaborated on stages of system development lifecycle from requirement gathering to production releases

## **Technical Specialist,** Alliance Software Inc.

05/2018 - 12/2020 | CEBU CITY (CAPITAL), Philippines

- Was Assigned on 4 different projects during the course of my time working on here, with each of their framework and specifications. was able to meet their expectation
- Work on code process from code development, code reviews, document creation and review, and code deployment handling.
- Work with teams and collaborated on stages of system development lifecycle from requirement gathering to production releases

#### References

#### Cherry Lyn Sta. Romana,

Dean, College of Computer Studies, CIT-U cstaromana@gmail.com

**Renato Taer**, *Project manager*, Fullscale Inc. rtaer@fullscale.io